Sir, I cannot have you filming here.
What's that?
You cannot be filming here.
There's too many private people.
I'm not telling him I told you this.
The guy that just pulled up
in the 4058, the rough Ferrari,
you should go talk to him.
But you cannot be filming him here.
He's a billionaire.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, is this your Ferrari?
Yeah.
How did you get rich, man?
What did you do to get a Ferrari?
I know you, dude.
What's your name?
Scooter.
Scooter Bronco.
What was the most amount of
money you made in a single year?
I sold my company years ago.
You want to know how much
I've seen you do this before?
How much did you sell your company for?
I sold the company for over a billion dollars.
What was the exact exit price?
1.5 billion pounds.
Not those cheap dollars.
The pounds.
Kobe Bryant was part of Body Armor, right?
Yeah.
How much did you have to pay Kobe Bryant?
Nothing.
He paid me.
What do you mean?
He invested $6 million to start in the company.
What did that turn into?
$415 million.
Are you serious?
Have you ever been broke before?
Oh, my God, dude.
I literally had to borrow.
When I was married to my wife with four kids,
had to borrow $200 from my mom.
Was $13 million in debt, had
no money, and paid it all back.
Please.
Did not.
Yeah.
You made billions of dollars throughout your career.
Are you happy now?
Huh.
Oh, wow.
You ask good questions.
Um, I don't think that's how life works.
Um.
I've interviewed over 40 billionaires,
and I've asked every single one
of them how they truly got rich
and how they built their billion-dollar companies.
But there's one question that
I've never asked them until now.
Are they actually happy?
So over the next few days,
I'll be in two of the wealthiest hubs in America,
Beverly Hills and Las Vegas,
to interview not one,
not two,
not three,
but four billionaires.
From tech founders to investors
to people who've made billions of dollars in exits
to find out if all the sacrifice
and hard work it takes to get rich
is actually worth it.
So let's go find out
if money can actually buy happiness.
All right, you guys.
So we are right now headed
to go meet up with and interview
our first billionaire out here in Beverly Hills, you guys.
Now, who is this billionaire?
This is the guy that has built some
of the biggest beverage brands in the entire world.
For example,
you ever had one of these right here?
Body armor?
Yeah, he sold body armor
to Coca-Cola for over $5 billion.
Or how about one of these or one of these?
These are all companies that he himself has
sold for hundreds of millions and billions of dollars.
Okay, but today we find out if
those billions of dollars actually made him happy.
We're not just going to be
getting the secret to getting rich,
but whether or not money actually can buy happiness.
Let's go see what he has to say.
How are you doing, my man?
This is Liam.
How are you doing, man?
I'm good, man.
Nice to meet you.
We were letting them know you
built everybody's favorite gas station drink.
That's it, baby.
That's the truth.
That's how we roll.
Today, we're going to be figuring out
the secrets to building a billion-dollar brand.
Yep.
And we're also going to be asking you if
the millions and billions of dollars actually leads to happiness.
That's what we're trying to figure out today.
Right.
So we're going to be talking about everything.
It ain't bad.
Right?
Definitely not.
That's it right there.
He's good like a kid.
How old are you today?
How old are you?
68 years old.
Yeah.
So you're a 68-year-old billionaire.
And you're still building companies.
I'm still going at it.
And I love what I do.
It keeps me young.
How much do you work?
How many hours a day do you work?
I don't work.
I was working all day before you came here.
I'm a young 68.
Most people think I'm 50.
I'm in shape.
I swim every day for an
hour and a half at the pool.
Money stays in shape.
And that's what I do.
I love what I do.
And what else am I going to do?
Land a beach?
I'm not that great at golf.
You know, I got the team.
I got my family.
I got over 500 employees.
And they're all driven with one goal, to win.
What was the most amount of money?
The money that you made in a single day.
In a single day?
Yeah.
When I sold Body Armor in October of 2021.
How much did you make?
A lot.
Give me a range.
How much?
Half a billion.
Half a billion dollars?
Yeah.
And how about for the company?
We made $5 billion.
About $5 billion for the business.
You made billions of dollars throughout your career.
Are you happy now?
Yeah, I'm ecstatic.
You are?
Yeah, I'm more ecstatic that you're here.
Why are a lot of billionaires miserable, though?
Because you hear people talk about it
all the time, how they're not happy.
Because money's not the answer to all.
I have a great life.
I have a great family.
I work.
I have my wife, my son, my daughter.
And we're very close.
We're all involved in some fashion in the businesses.
Everyone has great houses.
Everybody lives in great places.
We're good.
My senior executives have great lives.
They all made a lot of money.
And they want to keep doing it.
So you take care of your people?
Yes.
You have to?
Yeah, you got to.
Everyone has to get in the game.
Even my assistants.
They made a million dollars.
People working in the warehouse.
You made sure everybody ate when you sold your company.
Exactly.
We share the prize.
Do you think a lot of people forget about
that and they don't take care of their people?
Some people.
Some people do.
Yeah.
I'm going to challenge you.
As a billionaire, what is the best piece
of advice that you've ever received throughout your career?
I would say surround yourself with good people.
Make sure the first one works.
And make sure you leverage all those
guys that made money in your first deal.
They go in your second deal.
Then they go in your third deal.
And then it keeps going.
Honestly, I can raise $100 million in
one day if I start another company.
Because you know all the right people.
I know all the right people.
I've been blessed.
We talked about how you and all the billionaires that you
know, what is that one trait they all have in common?
They're killers.
They want to win.
They want to disrupt.
And they work their asses off.
Like Kobe.
Mamba mentality.
Dude, he works out until he passes out.
Every morning.
You've never seen dedication like him.
Kobe Bryant was part of Body Armor, right?
Yeah.
So how much did you have to pay Kobe Bryant?
Nothing.
He paid me.
What do you mean?
He wanted to get in the company.
He loved the product.
He invested $6 million to start in the company.
He invested $6 million in your company?
Yes.
What did that turn into?
$450 million.
Are you serious?
Well, he also got talent
marketing shares on top of that.
He was the director of sports marketing.
When Kobe Bryant calls the athletes to
come for a commercial, they all show up.
Harden came into Body Armor because of Kobe.
Give me the deepest life quote you've ever heard.
From Vince Lombardi.
My father used to say this.
It's not the big that eat the small.
It's the fast that eat the slow.
That's my famous quote in beverage.
Speed is important in business.
Dude, if you sit on your
hands, competition just runs you over.
68 today.
If me and you died tomorrow and you had one more
message to leave with the younger generation, what would that be?
Do what you love.
Because you won't have a job.
You got amazing advice, sir.
Thank you for your time, my friend.
And I connect with all the billionaires I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Yeah, of course.
Look, you guys, that's a happy billionaire right there.
Okay, look.
He said that money cannot be
the only thing to make you happy.
But look, he made a lot of other people rich.
Right?
He had the people that were custodians making money.
Man, the janitors, I think he said.
Man, so it just goes to show the more money you make other people,
the more money you're going to make and the happier you're going to be.
Great interview out here in Beverly Hills.
We got to go find this
next billionaire out here, you guys.
How they got rich.
Whether or not that money buys happen.
Come on.
All right, guys.
So we are right now headed to
go meet up with our next billionaire.
But this billionaire is not from the United States.
He's not from America.
No, no, no.
He's from the UK.
And he created and built the largest
phone retailer in all of the United Kingdom.
One of the biggest ones in Europe, I believe.
He sold his company back in 2006 for $1.6 billion.
And according to Forbes, he's worth
over $3 billion worth of fees.
We're about to link up with another billionaire to figure out if the
sacrifice and what it took to become a billionaire is really worth it.
Let's go see what he says.
What's going on, guys?
How you doing?
John, how you doing, my friend?
I'm James.
James.
Great to meet you, my friend.
Thanks for coming out to do an interview, man.
Pleasure.
I really appreciate that, man.
John, I have one rule for all my interviews.
There's no holding back at all.
We're going to give the younger generation a blueprint on how to
really become successful and make it in today's world like you did.
Can we make that happen?
We can try.
What was your main business
for the people that don't know?
Right.
So for the people that don't know, and of course
they won't know because all my business was UK-centric and European-centric.
And that was mobile phones.
And it was every aspect of mobile phones right
the way through from service provision, retailing, distribution, wholesale.
It was everything.
And I built.
I built that up from 1986 to 2006 from one man right
the way through to 12,000 people and a sellout of 1.5 billion pounds.
Not those cheap dollars.
Pounds.
The pounds, my man.
My man, I appreciate that.
They're about to get a billion dollars worth
of gain from you right here, my man.
So let's make it happen.
Did you come from a lot of money?
Like, were your parents rich?
My dad was a traveling salesman and
my mother was a post room manager.
So I suppose you could say definitely not.
Did 20-year-old you have any idea that
you were going to become a billionaire?
No, no, no.
No, no.
I grew up in the back streets
of Stoke-on-Trent in a tiny little house.
I had no money and no inspiration.
There's nobody around me to inspire me at all.
So no, I had no clue.
I always knew I was going to be successful.
Why?
A childhood dream I had
when I was eight years old.
And my dream was that I would be driving around in
a chauffeur-driven Rolls Royce, handing five pound notes out to poor people.
And that dream had to be fulfilled.
But in fulfilling that dream, nowhere
in that dream was I a billionaire.
You know, I was just successful and wealthy and charitable.
So you've made billions of dollars throughout your career.
You're 73 now.
Are you happy today?
You know, happiness is a relative subject, isn't it?
You know, I'm always challenged and
I'm happy when I achieve challenges.
So, for instance, on the 19th of July, I'm doing something that's impossible for me,
which is the Atape de Tour, the Tour de France cycling race up in the Alps.
It's an impossible challenge for me.
If I achieve anywhere near that, I'll be quite happy.
And then life is full of happiness
and full of sadness and full of issues.
So, yeah, I'm overall happy.
But I'm not content.
I'm not a good person.
I'm always struggling to achieve the next thing.
And you mentioned your dad was a travel salesman.
Are you a good salesman?
I don't think you're going to get to
where I am without being a good salesman.
What was your secret to sales?
If you could give me one piece of sales
advice that's not taught in a textbook or business
school.
Integrity.
You got to keep your word.
Beyond that, when people used to ask me
what are these mobile phones like, I would say
they're absolutely dreadful.
I said there'll be times when all you want to
do is throw it on the floor and stamp on
it.
And they said, well, that's strange.
The guy down the road I've been to said that.
They're perfect.
They're just like the ordinary home telephone.
I said, well, that's complete rubbish.
I said, they're absolutely dreadful.
But if you need one,
what are you going to do?
It's a unique piece of equipment
and you're going to buy one.
But expect it to be not very good.
And I never lost a sale ever because the truth.
And that was the truth.
But I used the truth to my
advantage to gain credibility with the customer.
So the guy down the road that told him
it was just like using a home telephone lost
all his credibility as a result of
me telling them that it was rubbish.
Correct me if I'm wrong.
Taxes are crazy in the UK.
Yeah.
Do you have a tax hack for anybody in business?
I believe that you should pay your taxes
in the country that you've made your money in.
There's a lack of humanitarianism on this planet.
So you paid your taxes?
I paid all my taxes
on the sale of the business.
What's the most amount of money
you paid in taxes in one year?
200 million.
You paid 200 million in taxes?
Yeah.
And I could have avoided it by moving to Monaco.
Why did you not do that?
Because I feel that the poor people need help.
So you did it for the goodness of other people?
Well, I didn't want to leave the UK.
I support the UK.
You know, I'm very patriotic.
And if I take my money away from the UK.
Then what does society do?
What happens to the country?
But would you say that most billionaires would not
choose to do that and they'd be a little
bit more greedy?
By and large, yes, to some extent.
I don't find many people that properly agree with me.
One of the favorite arguments that they give me
is, well, don't pay your tax, go to Monaco
and give even more to charity.
But the people that say that, surprisingly, avoid
the tax and don't give a lot to charity
or anything.
I just think we all have to work harder
to make the human race better, to make the planet
better.
John.
If you had one more tomorrow and you
had one more message to leave with the younger
generation, what would that be?
To the younger generation?
One more message.
Give me the best life advice you could
give to them in these last 20 seconds.
Like I told my kids, really, which
is I'm not bothered about you being rich.
I want you to leave the world a
better place than you found it and be happy.
And if on top of that, you can be
very successful in your career, in your money making, then
that's utopia.
But at least try and be happy and leave
the world a better place than you found it.
Can I tell you something?
I've done over a thousand interviews.
I've interviewed over 40 billionaires.
This is one of the best interviews
I've ever done in my life, man.
You tell everybody that.
No, I promise you I don't.
You can ask them.
Thank you so much for your time, man.
Pleasure.
This was incredible, man.
I connect with all the billionaires I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Sure.
Guys, we just finished interviewing our second
billionaire of this video, but I need you
to listen to me very carefully for one
second because next week I'm doing something insane
for you.
As a matter of fact, I'm hosting the
craziest event that I've ever hosted for the School
of Hard Knocks family.
On Tuesday, March 17th, I'm
hosting billionaire day number three.
This is a one day live event where I'm
going to be hosting three live zoom calls with three
different billionaire entrepreneurs.
I'm going to be doing a lot of things.
You want to know the wild part?
You're not just going to be
watching them like you are right here.
You'll actually be able to ask them your
questions directly about your business, how to scale,
how to invest, how to sell
like millionaires and billionaires do anything.
But first, let me show you who's coming first.
We're going to have Vic Keller, who built
and sold nine companies, three of them to
Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway.
Then I'm having an AI billionaire come on.
David Stout owns a company that's valued
at over two and a half billion dollars.
And lastly, Forbes Riley, who's known as
one of the greatest saleswoman of all time.
And she herself has sold over two million.
She's sold over two billion dollars throughout her career.
Look, these are the kinds of people whose
advice can change the trajectory of your business
overnight.
And I know that firsthand because the only
reason I've been able to build a multimillion
dollar business so young is because of the
access I had to learn directly from the millionaires
and the billionaires that I interview on this channel.
And now I'm giving you that same access.
And normally people would have to pay
thousands of dollars for something like this.
But right now, if you're still watching this,
you can join and get access for free.
There's only one catch.
There will be no recordings or replays to billionaire day.
So if you're watching this right now,
you can join and get access for free.
There's only one catch.
There's only one way to get access for free.
So if you're not here
live, you're going to miss it.
So if you want access to billionaire day part
three on March 17th, all you have to do is
go down right now.
Click the link in the description in
this video to grab your spot now.
I can't wait to see you
live next week on March 17th.
That being said, let's go get our next interview.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, sir.
Is this your G wagon?
Yeah.
How did you get rich, man?
What did you do to get a G wagon, man?
I recognize you.
I know your stuff from the internet.
What'd you do, man?
I worked in the entertainment industry for
a long time and invested in entrepreneurs.
You do good stuff, man.
I've seen it before.
What's your name?
Scooter.
Scooter Braun.
And what was the most amount of
money you made in a single year?
I sold my company years ago.
You want to know how much?
I've seen you do this before.
How much did you sell your company for?
I sold the company for over a billion dollars.
Over a billion dollars?
Yeah.
What was the exact exit price?
I mean, I go all over the world interviewing billionaires.
You've seen the channel before.
I have seen it.
That's why I'm so uncomfortable right
now, but I appreciate what you do.
Can I interview you for a minute real quick?
Is that okay?
Yeah, sure.
How long have you been an entrepreneur?
Since I was a kid.
I figured out a way to not be dependent, but
I started the company when I was 19 in college.
What was that defining moment in your life
where you had that mindset shift where you're
like, man, I'm going to go out there, make
a name for myself, and become one of the biggest
in the entertainment space that has ever seen?
For me, I was really, really young when I
started, so I was probably too dumb and too
ignorant to know that you probably
shouldn't be able to do this.
I think it was that blind belief.
I saw someone do an interview recently,
and they said that really great entrepreneurs
are delusional.
And I definitely was probably a little delusional when
I was younger that you can go and do
this.
And I think nothing great ever came from realistic ideas.
The only great things come from being unrealistic.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yeah, when I was first starting, everyone
thought I was killing it, but really, every
time I'd make money, I'd spend it
to kind of fake it to make it.
And I remember ordering Domino's pizza and realizing
I did not have enough cash to pay.
And I had this change jar that me and my roommates
had by the door, and I had to open it up and
pay for Domino's with change.
And I never forgot that because I always
say success and failure really live next door
to each other, really live next door.
And whenever you think it's going to fall
apart, that's when you've got to go with that
extra mile so that you
find out success is right there.
What year was that that you couldn't afford pizza?
Probably 23 years old.
I'm 44 now, so 21 years ago.
Twenty years ago, would you have any idea
then that you would end up selling a company
for over a billion dollars?
You know what's really funny?
When I first started, I wanted to do that.
I wanted to achieve that billion dollars.
And then I realized making 10 grand was really hard.
And I went and spoke to a guy in Atlanta
that I really admired, and he gave me a number
of 10 million of like, that's what
it would take to have his lifestyle.
And I really that was my goal.
I was like, I want to 10 million.
I want to have a beautiful family.
I want to have kids.
And, you know, my life changed.
And I remember when I passed that number, I
felt like, you know, what is it all for?
It felt empty.
And then my pops gave me some really good advice.
He said, well, what do you love to do?
And I said, I love being with my friends.
I love giving away tickets.
I love, you know, talking to
a random entrepreneur and helping them.
I love the adventure of life.
And he goes, well, I think money could be
a way to make you, you know, burdensome and
you could be tied up by it.
Or money could be something that sets you free
to do all of those things more and more
in your life.
So you are now the 44th billionaire that I've interviewed.
Are you happy now?
I don't think that's how life works.
I think life is ebbs and flows.
And there's days where you're really, really happy.
And there's days where you're sad.
And everybody, whether you have $10 or a
billion dollars or someone who has $100 billion, everyone's
having a human experience.
And what I've seen from people that have a
lot more money than me, who I've become friends
with, you know, they at
times can feel very, very empty.
And I think you don't need $200 billion
to start the work of going inside yourself and
figuring out who you are.
So if you want a tip, you want to, you
know, a cheat code for the end game of success,
start doing work on yourself now and
start seeing who you are and valuing yourself.
And that's going to be
a lot more important than anything.
And I think that's what I've learned the
most about myself is that you're going to
be able to do more
than making any amount of money.
You were in the entertainment business for decades.
For the people that don't
know, what was your business like?
What business made you the most
amount of money throughout your career?
We built a record label.
We built a publishing company.
We built a TV and film production company.
You know, for me, I never
wanted to be defined by one industry.
I wanted to be defined as an entrepreneur.
And that, to me, is just
living in adventure every single day.
Did you have people that
doubted you in the business world?
Yeah, of course.
I was a knucklehead 19-year-old kid from
Atlanta, you know, Atlanta, Georgia, who's coming up
in the hip hop industry and throwing parties.
Everyone was like, what the hell is he talking about?
He's going to build this and build that.
I'm assuming you had people that thought you were crazy.
Yeah, they thought I was nuts.
But every great entrepreneur I've ever met has that story.
Like I said in the beginning, if
it was realistic, it wouldn't be great.
It has to be delusional.
It has to be unrealistic.
It has to be something.
It's this idea that if you are playing
baseball, if the Cy Young Award winner was pitching
and everyone got to get in line and try
and hit that ball, you could take as many swings
as you want.
And the winner, you know, if you hit it
out of the park, you get a million dollars.
It's the person who shuts everyone out,
who keeps swinging and everyone's saying, you're
a bum.
You don't have it.
You're a bum.
The person who just keeps swinging, keeps
swinging, keeps swinging until they hit that
home run.
The person who shuts out the noise,
that's the person who becomes the great entrepreneur.
I want to shift real quick to investing.
You've invested in some of the biggest
companies in the world early on, right?
What's the number one thing that you look
for in a business when you're making an investment
into them?
I try to see if the entrepreneurs burn the ships.
It's never about what the business is for me.
You said burn the ships?
Burn the ships.
It's never about the business.
Like everyone else wants to look at that and everything.
For me personally, I just like to look
at the eyes of the founder and how psychotic
are they?
Like how crazy are they?
How driven are they?
Will they burn the ships?
shifts will they shut out the noise and i've seen
that before i've seen it you know travis from uber
he had that you know daniel ek from spotify he
had that like there are certain people that are so
driven and determined that you look them in the
eye and you're like they're gonna find a way i
love that man you got amazing advice and
i i connect with all the billionaires i interview
could i get your contact yeah of course guys
we just wrapped up with the billionaire scooter bra
man and he just gave so much incredible advice in
that interview but guys i think he just gave us
the secret right there he said the money
does not define happiness he said whether you make
ten thousand dollars a hundred million a
billion dollars we're all going through the human
experience great interview out here in los angeles we
gotta keep this one rolling and go get this next
one you guys come on all right you guys so look
as you can see babe we got a change of plans right
now we are right now about to fly out from beverly
hills to las vegas to go meet up with some more
billionaires you guys we're going from city to
city we'll find our next billionaire figure out
how they got rich and whether or not they're happy
you guys come on guys we just got to our
destination las vegas some millionaires and billionaires
playground and look we got a mission we
gotta find another billionaire to complete this video
to really figure out and ask them if money
truly buys happiness is after they amass that billionaire
status that billion dollar network if that money
buys happiness so we're at a destination some of
the richest people coming to be here in las vegas
you guys come on real quick i had a question for
you how did you get rich sir there we go excuse
me sir question for you yes is this your rolls royce
is this i have a channel where i'm going to
be a billionaire and i'm going to be a billionaire
i interview millionaires and billionaires all over
the world to get advice to the younger
generations hey i know you is that your rolls royce
how did you get rich man bro yeah you private guy
yeah i got you my man excuse me sir sir how did
you get rich oh i'm not the person who asked no no no
no all right but i've seen you guys on
either tiktok or something what line of business are you
in sir you said medtech how did you i'm not the
person all right have a good one look as you can
see man look these guys out here in
vegas man the millionaires and billionaires playground look they
look i'm not going to stop until i find
another billionaire to make this video even better for
you guys come on sir i cannot have you
filming here what's that you cannot be filming there's
too many private people not telling him i told you
this the guy that just pulled up in the 405
8 the rough ferrari you should go talk to him
but you cannot be filming him here he's a billionaire
you know him yeah i know what's he do private
equity i will go talk to him excuse me sir sir
is this your ferrari yeah how did you get rich man
what would you do to get a ferrari i know you did
equity well i'm wall street guy yeah how long were
you in the money business 36 years over these 36
years what was the most amount of money you made
a single year on paper a billion six maybe 1.6
billion yeah well that i took a company public that
i owned half of and it first opened at like
3.3 billion 3.5 billion or so can i interview you
for a minute i envy billionaires all over the world
to help the younger generation sure for sure is that
cool yeah i got one rule for all my interviews
there's no holding back we're going to give them
the blueprint right here on how to build a million
and billion dollar company sure can we make that
happen there's only three ways to make money you
only leverage people you leverage time you leverage
money you leverage money you leverage money you
leverage money you leverage money you leverage
leverage money right that's the only way to make money
you have to do one of those three right like
let's say you're a lawyer and you work for
somebody else you're selling your time you're not going to
get rich you'll be comfortable you leverage people by
becoming a lawyer and then starting a law firm
now you're making money on all the people that
are working for you so you're leveraging time and
money right that's game right there yeah right and
there you go you can't get rich working for
anybody i cannot i'm not i'm unemployable no one
will hire me why because i'm a lunatic like
are you crazy i'm crazy yeah and you couldn't pay
me what i'd want to get paid and then if you
leverage i'll give you an example i think
i'm meeting one of my analysts right here jason he
works for me i leverage him so jason what's up
brother so here we are this is this is vegas
so he is a total professional gamble the best black
check player ever but i when i started my
hedge fund again six seven eight years ago yeah about
seven so he's a he's a mathematical genius i'm
not so i leverage people by hiring good people that
have a different skill set and then put them to
work and let them do their thing you've made a ton
of money throughout your crew but are you happy
today oh i'm the happiest i've ever been in my
whole life how do you how old are you i'm uh
56. and you're really happy to be here yeah i'm really
happy yeah i've been married to the same woman
for 22 years i have four kids you've been faithful
well you know that's funny you say that when i
uh married her i told her that's a really interesting
story i said i can't be faithful she's like what the
hell i go i can't be but if you're with me on
the journey we can do everything together but ultimately
over time i just dug her so much and
she became she's such a great human being that
i became massively only thinking about her and so
i'm completely faithful which is crazy but you're
the happiest you've ever been the happiest i've
ever been have you ever been broke before oh my
god dude i literally had to borrow when i was
four kids had to borrow 200 from my mom was 13
million in debt had no money and paid it all back
you did not yeah when you were negative 13
million dollars in debt what were you telling yourself i
was depressed and i had a i have a
mentor named steve caspy he's one of the richest developers
in new york city and he stuck with me even when i
lost the money he gave me and he made it all back
tenfold but you need to have people that you can
network with i read a book when i was young called
think and grow rich by napoleon hill and people
don't read it today but if they read it they
understand that you can you can network
with people and this is going to sound
a little crazy but you've got to put
yourself in a position to understand what others would
do that have made it and get the best advice even
if they're not around read about it i do a ton of
reading i read so many books people would
just their head would spin but i'd probably consume
50 books a year do you actually yeah oh
yeah oh yeah what is your number one book recommendation
for anybody in business think and grow rich by
napoleon hill the road less travel which is a
psychological book by m scott peck if you're
not god-fearing like i'm a god-fearing guy you believe
in god oh for sure i do i absolutely know
that god exists how do you know that because i effectively
believe that everything that's put in front of you is
for a reason and you have to learn how to pay
attention to the reason so i don't believe in
god in the sense of organized religion i believe that
there's some greater scheme for you and you're
getting the message the whole time but are you
really paying attention to it are you really being
honest with what you're being told my failures have
only led to my success those failures happen for a
reason and if you look at it that way it's easier
to deal with but i completely believe in god how
old are you now 56. if me and you died tomorrow
and you had one more message to leave with
the younger generation what would that be oh wow you
had a little bit more i think about this a little
bit more so i think i'm going to ask you a little
bit more about what's going on with the social
network and what's going on with the crime and
a lot of people have a lot of questions you want to
go as fast as you can but you also want to take
your time none of these things you see like
on the social network and all these things where the
person started their dorm room and suddenly they
were billionaire that doesn't exist it's not real
it's hollywood i've been doing this literally 36 years
since i was 20. i think all my failures were
lessons that i was doing it wrong and i needed
to pay attention but i never quit that's one thing
i'll tell you is my wife will say this i never give up never never never you're
going to have to kill me and then even then i have a legacy i have kids
I love it.
You've got amazing advice, sir.
Appreciate it.
Thank you for your time.
And I connect with all the
millionaires and billionaires that I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Oh, yeah, for sure.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
Guys, that's a wrap on today's video, man.
I need you guys to like and subscribe
for amazing content coming every week to the School
of Hard Knocks.
Man, we just interviewed four billionaires in one video.
So like and subscribe, like I said, and go
down right now to the link in the description
of this video because you can get
access to the number one most powerful entrepreneur
community and network in the entire world
called the School of Mentors, where every
single week you can hop on live
calls and get mentored directly from the millionaires
and billionaires that I interview on this channel.
I can't wait to see you on the inside.
That being said, I'll see you in the next episode.